what up through my Prius right now when
caught my eyes Prius go down south going
hiking I don't have a phone mount so
it's very precariously put on the
dashboard and we're gonna see if open
pilots is capable of driving so well
that it won't fall but you'll probably
fall Skokie so be ready you know hang on
to something
put your put your vlog belts on what
does take pulse at all right so let me
just make this turn myself I don't have
a great pan in this car and leave a
white panda about a great panda it might
have made that turn for me gray pandas
our firmware is coming along super
nicely for them I'm some driving he's
mighty on up here you see my Comus maze
up there
what up I like how the Prius like has
this thing I just have my phone put just
like right on here yeah so what are we
going to talk about today check out my
Venice Beach California shirt this is
this California guys you know this is
this is exciting exciting shit I love
having you know this system
[Music]
yeah I don't know I really have not much
plan to talk about today mostly we're
just gonna cruise anyone has any
questions and I'm happy to answer them I
mean unfortunately I do have to press
the resume button on the Prius
so the Prius does work and stop and go
but you have to press resume which kind
of sucks that's the only real downside
and that is baked into the Prius engine
firmware but once we get Prius hacks
that is very possible the 2018 Civic
that one works
2018 Civic is good cruising here
you want to order soon how far out are
great pandas what does it say four to
twelve weeks up red light see now that
would be nice that would have been that
would have been a very nice experience
if the car had stopped for that red
light for me it should have it should we
got it we got to get them lights in
there she'll see God
yeah my my eon that bro next to me
vlog belts on
[Music]
are there steps to install for the
cinema
how many times before the HD road
manager said Tesla Hardware always chaos
a little dream I mean I don't think they
have redundant actuators I think if you
truly want to get to level 4 you're
gonna have a problem where your
actuators need like an extra level or
four guns you think about it like a
backup parachute right that was me doing
the acceleration to be honest I've open
pilot took off from that you probably
wouldn't have fallen
yeah let's go
I'm going to come up on another red
light red lights are disrupting my
experience right now we need the red
lights to be added into open pilot so if
anyone out there from Khomeini is
watching we need we need red lights
this is disrupting my experience my self
driving experience is ruined by this
terrible red light and this pedestrian
she's around she's crossing
appropriately good time oh yeah we don't
see four actuators right so here's how I
kind of think level threes actually go
um stack cream on it
so he'll shoot blogs like Logan come on
Ari um here's my thing level threes
actually gonna play out I think that
level three is basically gonna say that
most failures are detectable but you'll
still very occasionally have an
emergency failure where the human needs
to be immediately available consider
like an actuator failure to be an
emergency failure right if you're
reading a book or you're using your
phone which is what level three is gonna
let you do um you know you can be alert
pretty quickly if you have something
like an actuator failure right and we
have to make sure that that that that
transition is kind of seamless like if
everything in the car screams break
you'll be on the brake within two
seconds it's not even thinking about it
um and you know you should always have
you should always have at least two
seconds so if there is an actuator
failure we should know really really
quickly and that's what is doable in
kind of a level-3 scenario um what's not
doable level three scenario is like
sending these cars out on the road with
literally no people
so the yeah I mean you're just gonna
need more actuator redundancy and that's
what I think Tesla lacks um make your
doesn't steer full of right some
steering torque limits or as long as you
get the software correct it's not that
dangerous to raise it I mean as long as
you're sure that you're detecting if the
user is overriding this Sunday I don't
know if I could freestyle did I guess we
just put my speed up here I hate this we
got to override this to the Prius like
right now I have to like tap this button
70 million times to get any sort of file
and they sort of raise up quickest
easiest way to reverse engineer with
panda Cabana Andy on you see my Sun
Visor mostly I can tell you back a
little bit assuming we're not
accelerating or decelerating you might
fall the more I tell you back the more
likely you are to fall but yeah so let's
drive it right now and the motor is even
capable of full torque oh yeah oh yeah
this Prius motor is capable for a full a
full torque
how much for a wrap feature guys if you
show me that you have like traction and
you want me to come on and do a 60 and
I'll give you I'll give you 16 bars for
free on that kind of wrapper and one of
the chill wrappers you know by the way
if you haven't checked it out
soundcloud.com slash Tom Cruise that's
Tom Cruise with two zeros open pilot is
so much smoother on the brake to the
accelerator than I am Tom Cruise any
plans for bigger Aeon no no yawns are a
good size
we don't need bigger yachts
all right come on
let's think it use a little bit more
pickup I think in the one of the next
releases we're gonna raise the
acceleration limit from it's right now
at 0.15 G our Civic motors capable of
full torque I don't know um I don't
think the 404 hoody the hoody 404 well
oh well hoodies look good while that
lasted um I don't know about the Civic I
had some issues with the ILX even though
I had full armor mods giving me all the
torque oh it has a model bias issue this
is annoying we need new models coming
someday come except well
support for other cars now only Honda's
and Toyota
all that other stuff I lied we're
actually going to be buying Eddie a
Honda Accord so that's what we are going
to we're gonna have so Honda Accord the
reason we support Honda's at Toyota's is
because these features are standard the
features that we need in order to
support open powder standard and not
just on high trim levels if what you
need is high trim levels it's just not
going to work
no no outie I put up a 10k bounty that's
the best I can do if you guys want to
support Audi if somebody out there
manage just to support Audi $10,000 keep
pipe or some way to avoid fan noise does
the fan eyes bother you that much the
new control policy is much much better
the fan noise only bothers me when it's
at full speed I don't think we go at
full speed too much I don't know maybe
you read like Arizona where it's a
hundred ten degrees out hey if somebody
had support for Kia Soul
I'll give them I mean Morgan I'll give
Subaru but why not an application built
into car dashboards that's not a good
idea I'm not writing mods for every
stupid dashboard of every car the EON is
honestly so fine where it is
best help guide for reverse engineer got
to do it yourself man
oh the Toyota this there's no limits
really we limit the torque way more than
what the controller allows you can get a
lot of torque from these guys especially
on cars like the Corolla
so the Corolla has the same torque limit
as the rav4 but to Corolla what he's
like looks like a thousand pounds less
so that that thing will really fly
the Prius has this issue and we're
getting it right now where the steering
is a little bit sticky guys remember
from freshman physics where you learn
about static friction and kinetic
friction so once things are sliding they
have less friction but you have to
overcome static friction first the Prius
has a little bit of static friction on
the wheel so we can probably improve
this by using a better controller
I'm is it possible to do full stop and
go on a Corolla not without engine mods
not without not without PCF mods the
brake will take you all the way to zero
but right now you we can only accelerate
when you're above 20 no I don't give a
shit about building things into the
dashboard it's a stupid ways to pack
however taking an IQ test yeah exit
right to exit 43 eight checkout ways
I've got ways that my other people can
write dashboard stuff you have you wanna
waste your time it's not worth it like
the best you could consider doing is
tapping into something like Android auto
heartbreaking heartbreaking
heartbreaking I don't like that
my dad gonna become a scope yeah he's a
scope II if you watch us some of these
that wasn't open pilot heartbreaking
that was the guy in front of me
heartbreaking
opinions on tenses well y'all know I'm a
tensorflow fan I try to use PI torch but
you know where it work I torches for fun
tensorflow is for work I've been doing
that much machine learning lately like
you know the truth is a simple model
with a good product around it is better
than a complex model with a bad product
around it so we're doing a lot more on
the product side superbrain stacks only
point seven aisle xtogo so mr. Warren
I like ways when I go to CMU for was it
worth it there's a few courses that are
very good I had a few professors who I
really liked avoid any sort of freshman
shit also you know I probably talked
about this the US universities are taken
over by an ideological disease so it may
not be the kind of place you want to be
at right now you might want to wait for
that disease to be cured
so yeah I mean the truth is about any
store university education is you can
find better stuff on the Internet
probably that you'll find in any college
I took operating systems in compilers
Carnegie Mellon I really enjoyed both
those classes I got a lot out of them
how can you start learning excite
International Airport I come from like
like old-school hacker culture never ask
a question like that that's not a good
question right how can you start
learning I mean you know the answer to
that is Google Google just Google you
want to start writing greater read
trying to do great right that's that say
you know how can I start learning is not
a good question who's a great Eric
Raymond has this great blog post where
he talks about my blog post it's more of
like an FAQ how to ask good questions
and it's important it's it's a loss
scale
you can get cloned you could try to read
the code no I mean some Senate right to
exist for Sony projects that's the
attack but you can read everything and
like read the code read read our medium
post read everything and all these
things are just a Google away aim of our
ml Leto it's a secret I'm some some some
comm employees you guys have never heard
about because they like privacy we
respect respect the privacy of our
employees who choose privacy I mean you
guys know you guys know Eddy you guys
know Ricardo you guys know Andy I'm not
going to the airport actually I'm
picking a friend up and then we are
gonna go hiking there was apparently a
plane crash in these woods so we're
gonna see if we can find the crashed
plane to the left my background
all right you heard that open pilot stay
to the left good open pilot goody-goody
yo tell you about my background well I
grew up in the suburbs
I listen to emo music and it made me the
person that I am today
Indiana Jones plan what am I doing with
Indiana Jones
no I'm just you know that song him and I
continue screaming it's too easy this
morning I said I got my hand
oh the Indiana Jones I said to people
like know about this is just like a real
thing
, army yo you guys know who the enemy is
right well favorite evoke bad ice ELISA
like brandy'wyne Senses Fail and shit in
high school it's real bad
some of these emo revival stuff is it's
like the world is a beautiful place
I'm longer afraid to die I love this I
love this stuff to stay relevant
you know pianos become the teeth a list
of merchant ships last night oh that's
good that's good
Oh big say anything fan oh the DMV
approve of karma I mean yeah so I'm
gonna tell you guys something I'm gonna
tell you guys something I heard this
from a secret source we're negotiating
with the DMV how the DMV defines an
autonomous vehicle so obviously everyone
knows like Tesla autopilot coming I open
pilot or not autonomous vehicles under
50 of these definition the definition
that was clawed out of the DMV in
private was if your car can make a
90-degree turn autonomously then it's an
autonomous vehicle so that's the
definition we use here in common so
almond pilot is not capable of making a
90-degree turn
like from a stop like that you know you
come to a stop sign to make a 90-degree
turn and because it's not yeah the DMV
approved sure um we've gotten anyways we
talked with to DMV a bit more than we
let on they talk to us they harass us
but hey that's kinda their job
um so guys who's the enemy who is the
enemy in the common army you guys know
how far away is stay further to the
trailer in the next Lane does our
infrastructure support that yeah we got
a hack beside radars on the cars
Pittsburgh is self-driving back up into
place it's alright Oh actually my friend
who I'm going with today we are we would
seem you together Ford is not the enemy
you guys for it is not the enemy the
real world that's getting close man
no Tesla's definitely not be gotta be
bad supers not to get me nature there we
go nature man that's who we're fighting
against here we're at war with nature
Ford is doing big things
yeah like f-150 is with big tires I'd
agree with that it's deep matte steel
wool steel wool open source and maps and
feel all they're good people
oh no I don't care about Subarus
everyone else on the road they're
playing the cooperative game with us
driving a cooperative game you guys know
I'm complacency I don't like to play you
know I don't like complacency
complacency sucks man see I want to live
forever and if I want to live forever I
can't be complacent got awesome I was
down at the house of kangaroos I love
Tigers now look at Australia for a few
years
autonomous car more mission last nature
no I said only nature like trees and
shit I mean nature like like like like
God right I mean nature like whoever
built like the laws of physics right
that's who we're trying to beat here
what do I think of Argo AI I don't know
I haven't seen shit from them they seem
to be part of the PR form foam PR Branch
afford hi I'm a new fan well my 19 you
are troll man I know you are troll troll
troll troll why did I back off the Tesla
development I don't know they're kind of
dicks to me like I don't know you want
to be a dick to me you can I'm still
gonna respect you sorry man will we lose
the brain if they don't make it not
research if I haven't liked reason shit
guys oh my god it's don't worry about
like the environment that stuff is just
like make sure we collect the data and
can rebuild it all if we want to what
partnership
I've never partnered with nobody
how can mobilize support a lot of models
with our aftermarket product because
it's gonna be a warning only product
only inhale a bubble I actually sell
something that drives your car how do
you prevent criminals oh no criminals
but might they do they might have a
slightly more leisurely commute to go a
rob the bank what is coming iCarly eyes
lit bras look at this guy bump it bump
it whatever he's bumping over there his
Lexus
here is music
do I think a 2013 Honda I don't know man
that's the bad question it's Sunday
Oh bad question George is the criminal
yeah criminal you guys how's it look hey
Judi criminal it's gotta be a victim
who's the victim right oh no oh no you
can send a suicide bombing bro put a
fucking Rock on the gas pedal or don't
cuz you're a dick
well theoretically man yeah bro like the
truth is like those people if you're
shit like that loses dicks and like it's
not about the technology they're always
gonna find ways to be Dex like that's
the problem so he was I was the victim
man I was oppressed bro what does common
need that's not well done well we always
need to hire more people and we don't
just hire more people we honestly need
to hire people who are capable of
managing other people management is
sucks like I don't know if you guys have
ever managed people but it sucks
waise I'm trusting you to tell me where
I gotta get off Fabien Silicon Valley
man now let me do some more good people
yeah oh you always need good people
right so we always need good people I my
thing is in nine minutes we're just
checking my ways here and my yawn what
if you use a ton of his choice to pull
your building and hide the building
you're gross
didn't-didn't the UH in the other State
Building used to be around here now a
bunch of autonomous trucks come take it
away
um that's not you about smart people
people need management for all sorts of
reasons I mean some smart people don't
need management but you know
management's kind of a disaster what's
coming I'm not building anybody go talk
about liability man I can't think of any
positive uses of I'm a big fan of Elon
selling the flamethrowers but like I'm
not selling the flamethrowers bullshit
tunku's rap video yeah support more cars
and add more cameras oh my god more
cameras as a fan question the problem is
not cameras and the problem is not car
support the problem is honestly right
now we need to get our localization down
to 10 centimeters everywhere we need to
launch our bottom ass open soy's HD maps
make a soda can and I don't know my set
speed I don't like this thing
accelerates way too slowly we got out we
got a bump up that got Excel
I don't think I paired the Bluetooth
before but there's a little problem the
Aeons right now because european oh you
mean the little red lights don't worry
you can see them localization is great
pandas yeah we're no local dishes a lot
of software working on the back end our
localization software localization teams
actually at work right now we got a late
cut in here we got a late cut in bros
like cut it like cut it that's good it's
good good job ya know once we get
localization they'll be easy to roll it
out to everywhere we have like a three
million wild and we'll just spin up ten
thousand azure instances and just do it
you got to spend that as your money
right
hello men sunday scobie's i see my
driver being way more boring without you
guys attractive about is really boring
autonomous goons to do my bidding the
goons bro our harsh Jasper from 101
Dalmatians I mean private the ladies on
your dumb for wealthy clients why you
think I'm a whore you think I'm like one
of those Instagram girls it goes to
Dubai and puts other people's cars
none what's your fascination with low
gagging man low gang is the
fastest-growing gang on YouTube
we want to be the fastest growing army I
don't know what Apple tighten this I
mean that shit with like the seven light
hours on the roof
I don't like raspberry pies any big
updates before localization we got some
stuff planned localization with
lane-keeping help account gets washed
out yes forward collision alert Scheffer
and maybe only if we'll be good like
strawberry pies like apple pies man that
was pretty great
now resin fires kind of Academy yoga I
mean use a phone
honestly use a phone
no like like like it's just literally a
worse phone the people need like this is
what we do with neo ass right we made
Android actually usable yeah I don't
want to hear about more cameras gross
the problems not more cameras most of
all compiles dis engagements are not
caused by a lack of cameras to make an
iOS jailbreak well driving old wires
jailbreaks anymore why I'm County for
the fusion you know some least I could
do
I think you'll ever do camera processing
like HDR gap HDR's actually gonna launch
Ian's already support the young Harbor
already supports HDR we just need to
roll it out in software throw in
athletes we should have an athletics in
this car oh wait my sick minute I don't
the wheel
one point six miles I'm getting off at
Whipple Avenue a right Whipple
[Music]
you all hear that beep does a
disengagement there's a bit over to the
right lane so I can get off Whipple
Avenue down here in Palo Alto ever
there's a few people that call them
they're smarter than me can cameras do
better than humans yeah humans ain't
that great that's the hardest thing we
need to accomplish next uh-huh we got
some great stuff but Eddie's new car is
gonna be a Honda Accord we're gonna buy
a 2018 Honda Accord for Eddie like next
week true all Byam planets no don't buy
an apple addicts buy a grape and Abed
gray pandas are literally almost as good
as a plan X's right now wait'll you see
our software update do not mess with us
with a car me we have we have a few
issues we can see all the red lights
where's open source heading is the
future all open source parts are
anytime between this engagements I don't
know we had like five dis engagements on
this Drive and a few more on fire I can
be honest I haven't given it about the
ps4 I really I don't know one why would
I care
I've been the only games I play now we
have we have a vibe at an oculus at the
office so playing playing feed our games
on our 1080p eyes we don't just use it
for machine learning in aetherium mining
you driving a foot no driving a Prius
right now bro I said Prius there's no
ways up there on my Eon I love having
ways on the e on its policy it's a great
experience I'm so happy we kept that so
that's what I'm driving right now
yeah ps4 checkout pages pet pieces I put
a tent a bounty that's the best I can do
that's all we're doing for Audi who was
your new way I leader she's a secret um
when comma rap I don't do I don't do
third quarter man I rap without real
life I rap about I rap about emotion my
favorite video especially super hot
pretty happy with that but I'll see one
of the best VR experience is that oculus
like dumping the demo for the touch
controllers michaelis touches are so
nice just posted EPS hack guys be
extremely careful with the EPS hacks I
warned you get half a mile turn right on
Jefferson Avenue don't come to a full
stop I'd only have to press the button I
don't want to press the button go but I
let go go go
will you jailbreak the ps3 to help
market no I really I could not care less
about Sony about the ps3 about any of
that crap cars of the future Bros you
should keep your eyes on the road my
eyes are plenty on the road you guys oh
wow I don't want to hear that though 6
minute timeout yeah you know it's so
boring
driving impossible integrating with ways
to take exits yeah that's gonna happen
sort of you'll see
yeah I have one Titan b-but we have a
single Titan V it's a right pure Pixar
what's that 1,000 feet turn right
thank you ways
thank you open power for stopping me
safely beyond this lovely Honda Odyssey
Touring edition you bro should I pull up
next to him and tell him about open
pilots should I have Dan july's go
forward no no disengage me because I
press the wrong button I pressed Sat
instead of resume I regret my decision
immensely
I see the autopilot with the orange
video you mean the one with smashed into
a firetruck because these radars are
criminally bad don't even blame Tesla
for that honestly it's the radar makers
you guys we have the same problem George
can you say Billy I'm not kidding out of
bed well I just said it a lot of hacker
bros I'm an entrepreneur
no I'd never actually say that was his
joke face why Pacific oh we're not
actually supporting in Pacifica am i hi
do I use adderall I am not high right
now I had a cup of coffee and a maje
this morning honestly when I'm high I'm
a not driving cars and be a lot less
actually a lot less hyper I get a lot
more chill and I don't really take out
at all i smoke weed
turn right on Jefferson yeah he's got a
new car commas snapchat Bros should do
it should do it should we go all in on
the social Wow I've never actually been
to Redwood City
alright so I think this is my friend's
apartment right here this spot alright
true use the Prius South Park now that
shit sucks I can't see up there good
parking job bros yeah open pile of shit
park for us we could do it any more
cameras thank you for joining this
periscope I'm gonna text my friend going
hiking today I gotta pee I wonder if I
can leave my car here at Sunday I hope I
can alright thanks for joining scobie's
hope you enjoyed Sunday scope E and come
army keep you real thanks bro
geez